<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Servo</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Servo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>The Servo Project Developers</copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/governance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/</guid><description> Governance Technical Steering Committee Technical Charter Technical Steering Committee minutes Subcommittees Participation Agreement And Funding Charter</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/board/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/board/readme/</guid><description>Servo Project Fund The purpose of the Servo Project Fund is to raise, budget and spend funds in support of the Servo Project.
The Fund is governed by a Governing Board, as set out in the Fund Charter in the Participation Agreement . The Board is composed of Members, and representation from Mozilla, and from the Technical Steering Committee.
If your orgaziation is interested iun becoming a Member, please contact us at info@servo.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/charter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/charter/</guid><description>Technical Charter (the &amp;ldquo;Charter&amp;rdquo;) for Servo Project a Series of LF Projects, LLC Adopted September 16, 2020
This Charter sets forth the responsibilities and procedures for technical contribution to, and oversight of, the Servo open source project, which has been established as Servo Project a Series of LF Projects, LLC (the &amp;ldquo;Project&amp;rdquo;). LF Projects, LLC (&amp;ldquo;LF Projects&amp;rdquo;) is a Delaware series limited liability company. All contributors (including committers, maintainers, and other technical positions) and other participants in the Project (collectively, &amp;ldquo;Collaborators&amp;rdquo;) must comply with the terms of this Charter.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/infra-2020-11-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/infra-2020-11-27/</guid><description>attending: ajeffrey, paul, simonsapin, jdm
ajeffrey: first meeting of the infrastructure committee! hooray!
jdm: I’ve started CI experiments. Early stages; just trying to run a linux build inside a docker container that’s in docker hub.
ajeffrey: there’s a shared 1password account now.
simonsapin: Don’t expect to meaningfully contribute to future infrastructure work now; the AWS migration is all wrapped up at this point.
jdm: I made contact with github, but nothing to report yet.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/infra-2020-12-04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/infra-2020-12-04/</guid><description>attending: ajeffrey, simonsapin, jdm
ajeffrey: second infrastructure subcommittee meeting! I have added AWS credentials to the 1password account. jdm, can you verify you can make use of them?
action item: jdm test out AWS login.
simonsapin: Web UI for 1password doesn’t have import/export, and I don’t have access to the app any more. jdm, can I send you a file to import?
jdm: Yes. CI update: successfully ran a WPT chunk under github actions for linux.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-10-16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-10-16/</guid><description>Attending: ajeffrey, nox, manishearth, jdm, jack, ssapin, negge, paul
Alan: have to pull out of October OSS EU launch announcement because trademark transition is taking longer than expected. How’s the website?
Paul: Can have the edits applied and ready for linux foundation review within 10 days.
Alan: How’s the infrastructure?
Simon: To be clear, I don’t want to lead infrastructure long term, just want to help with transition. I’ve removed a bunch of Amazon volumes which should reduce the monthly billing.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-10-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-10-23/</guid><description>attending: ajeffrey, jdm, paul, simonsapin, manishearth
ajeffrey: most things are ground to a halt due right now. Can make progress on CI though.
simon: waiting on a few things, like domain name transfer from mozilla. Also AWS, which has homu and some other things - it will be easier to make a new account and transfer things over rather than trying to extract from mozilla. For copying, a new account will require some payment information, and that should be from the official project to avoid personal liability.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-10-30/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-10-30/</guid><description>attending: jdm, ajeffrey, paul, ddh, manishearth, simonsapin, nox
ajeffrey: Still waiting for Mozilla to complete process. LF folks are talking to Mozilla legal. Under discussion is CI and board stuff. No roadblocks yet. LF wants to know if we have any requests.
ddh: Any chance for money to extend CI runway?
ajeffrey: No chance of money. Maybe could ask for CI support, possibly in exchange for board. It is actually work for them to disentangle us from taskcluster.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-11-06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-11-06/</guid><description>attending: ajeffrey, jdm, simonsapin
ajeffrey: Since last time, LF has told us that discussions with Moz Legal are “moving forward”. Sensible dates for launch have been discussed, so Nov 19 is one possibility. We either go for right before US Thanksgiving or right after.
simonsapin: When’s that?
jdm: Nov 26.
ajeffrey: Only constraint is ensuring the website is nailed down by launch.
simonsapin: Should confirm with paul, but it feels like 20 days should be ok.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-11-13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-11-13/</guid><description>attending: ajeffrey, jdm, manish, simonsapin
ajeffrey: press embargo lifts on the 17th! various things will go private-&amp;gt;public on github, and LF wants one person to be a contact person for any interviews. Mozilla has OKed IP transfer and press materials. Need to be off of community taskcluster by May.
simonsapin: AWS - we now have a account with the prepaid card, so I was able to transfer everything from mozilla-servo aws account (ec2 machine running homu and other services, and the s3 buckets for build dependencies and nightly build archives, and the CDN for the downloads).</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-11-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/launch-2020-11-20/</guid><description>attending: jdm, asajeffrey, paul, simon, manish
ajeffrey: launch happened uneventfully! 200 people in zulip, people are asking questions. there was press coverage, lots of twitter notifications.
simonsapin: we talked with pietro from the rust team who told us we misinterpreted github’s CI limitations. public repos have no limitations on minutes for github actions. the main limitation right now is the available ram on the public pool of machines.
ajeffrey: what comparison between github macs versus the macstadium machines?</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/readme/</guid><description>Servo Technical Steering Committee The TSC is responsible for technical oversight of the Servo Project, as laid out in the charter .
Membership Current members:
Alan Jeffrey Anthony Ramine Connor Brewster Cheng-You Bai Delan Azabani Diane Hosfelt Emilio Cobos Álvarez Fernando Jiménez Moreno Gregory Terzian Jack Moffitt James Graham Josh Aas Josh Matthews (secretary) Keith Yeung Manuel Rego (chair) Manish Goregaokar Martin Robinson Oriol Brufau Patrick Walton Philip Lamb Paul Rouget Simon Sapin Meetings The TSC meets in public, and all minutes are published.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/tsc-2020-10-09/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/tsc-2020-10-09/</guid><description>Servo Technical Steering Committee Meeting Date: 2020-10-09 Location: Zoom
Agenda Welcome!
Select chair. Nominations:
Alan Jeffrey Select representative to the board. Nominations:
Same as chair Select other officers. Candidates:
Secretary (Nominations: Josh Matthews) Form subcommittees. Candidates:
Technical direction Launch Plan for future meetings
Any Other Business
Minutes Attending: jdm, asajeffrey, kvark, mrobinson, kichjang, larsberg, cybai, ferjm, paul, manishearth, simonsapin, cbrewster, jack, jgraham, nox, aas, emilio
Alan welcomes the inaugural technical steering committee.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/tsc/tsc-2020-12-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/tsc/tsc-2020-12-11/</guid><description>attending: ajeffrey, jdm, manishearth, mrobinson, simonsapin, ferjm, cybai, aas, emilio
ajeffrey: welcome to second TSC meeting for servo project. first order of business: question from public about recording the meeting.
jdm: do people want recording or just the minutes?
ajeffrey: probably the summary. one thing - a recording can include stuff about third parties which we might not want to be recorded permanently. i’m inclined to say we’re minuting but not recording.</description></item></channel></rss>